Thank you, captain.
Well?
The target is still in the same place.
Target is leaving the apartment.
Ten seconds.
Start the engine.
Underwear or no underwear today?
Be a little more professional, guys.
She's turning left.
She's going to her usual café.
May I take your order?
A tea with milk,
an orange juice and...
And a croissant.
It's already ordered.
Thank you.
Do you have a visual?
We have a visual.
She's drinking her tea.
Come again?
She's drinking her tea!
Did you ask for a tea, sir?
No, no. Thank you.
I'm looking for Ms. Elise Ward.
That's Ms. Ward over there.
Elise Ward?
- Yes, it's me.
- I have an envelope for you.
Somebody is talking to her.
Looks like a courier.
No, no. It's okay. It's a gift.
Goodbye.
- Take him.
- Let's get him.
Sir, stop! Police!
What's going on?
- You are under arrest.
- Financial Crimes Division.
Division what?
Guys, I'm working!
Daniel, get over there now.
Drive around to the other side! Go!
Turn right at the end.
Faster!
How about a photo?
Go right ahead.
Make me look good.
Memorize his face.
The train arrives in ten minutes.
As soon as he steps off, arrest him.
Understood.
The operation has been cancelled.
Return to headquarters. Quickly.
On the other side.
Welcome to Venezia, signora.
- He doesn't look like Pearce.
- Boss said he might not.
Grab him!
Boss wants him alive, you idiot!
She's coming back.
Prepare to intervene.
Headquarters!
Send me backup to the fruit market.
I have a nutcase who wants to jump.
Probably American.
Stop, stop! Please!
Don't do it!
Bastard!
Remember, don't shoot him!
They are back.
I come back tomorrow?
I don't think she actually knows.
No. Knife.
This guy is crazy.
This was the man on the boat.